okay this is happening now basically the u.n security council which is 15 countries including
china uk united states they were the ones who were supposed to vote and make a ceasefire and you saw
america say yeah actually no that guy so when that happened everyone's like well this still
can't keep going on and that is how 377 gets invoked it's when the actual other folks who are
not in the security council are like security council you're not doing your job i feel secure
and secure and so mauritania and egypt said we're invoking invocation now this has only been invoked
13 times and five out of the 13 times it was invoked because of israel so clearly we see who the menace
to society is i will also add though that if they end up voting for a ceasefire israel doesn't have
to heed it they can literally ignore it it says it in the actual writing for the record in the past
they have they have heeded so the vote is happening on december 12th at 3 p.m in new york if you want
to go outside the u.n and make your voice heard please do because this really could be a way to
get a permanent ceasefire implemented and we all know that it is long overdue